Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records 1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995) MS 3009-RG 5
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.I. Office of the President: Corporate Special Projects Staff: Edgar P. Smith Files, 1960-1966; 1.34 Linear feet in 2 record cartons and 1 flat folder
  Edgar Smith's files document his work for the President's Office pursuing new business ventures for Time Inc. including new magazine development and subsidiary acquisitions. His folder "Magazine search: Industrial" contains a copy of the advertisement Time Inc. placed in the Wall Street Journal in 1960 stating that an "Established publishing company wishes to buy or acquire interest in promising trade or general circulation magazines..."
  Records include correspondence of proposals and ideas forwarded to Smith by other Time Inc. executives such as Chairman of the Board Andrew Heiskell, President James Linen, Time Publisher Bernard Auer, and Manfred Gottfried, part of the original Time Inc. staff and in a corporate develoment role similar to Smith; correspondence with other publishing companies; and background information on the companies and their products. Records regarding a range of pursuits are in "New investments" and "Magazine search."
  The "New investments" folders includes records on the Silver Burdett textbook publishing company acquisition, possible acquisition of the Berlitz Schools of Languages, the sale of Time Inc.'s magazines Architectural Forum and House & Home, a declination from Houghton Mifflin for a merger with Time Inc., along with other possible magazine or book publisher acquisitions.
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed by the archivist.
  - Colonial Press, 1966 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 2-3)
  - Magazine project: Notes, circa 1961 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 4)
  - Magazine search: General, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 5-7)
  - Magazine search: Industrial Research, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 8-10)
  - Magazine search: Gottfried's file on Industrial Research, 1960 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 11)
  - New investments, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 4212, Folder 12-17)
  - Silver Burdett, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 604, Folder 1)
  - The Travelers Club: Trans-World Villas ads, 1962 (Offsite-box 604, Folder 2)
  - The Travelers Club: Trans-World Villas binder, 1962 (Offsite-box 604, Folder 3)
  - The Travelers Club: Travel orientation kit: Tour of France, [1962] (Offsite-box 604, Folder 4)
  - The Travelers Club: Travel orientation kit: Tour of France, [1962] (Offsite-box 4271, Folder 1)
  - TV Channels, 1960 (Offsite-box 604, Folder 5)
- Series III.A. Corporate Secretary and Vice President P. Peter Sheppe Files on Pioneer Press Sale, 1973-1984; 0.6 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  P. Peter Sheppe Records on Pioneer Press Sale contains his records as vice president and secretary regarding the sale of this Time Inc. subsidiary. Records include correspondence and memoranda from group vice president Charles Bear, correspondence regarding possible buyers, valuation reports, and sale timelines.
  - The Pattis Group, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 1-2)
  - Pofcher Company [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Purcell, John: Mengel, McCabe & Co., Inc., 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 3)
  - Purcell, John: Mengel, McCabe & Co., Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R16)
  - "Q" magazine, 1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 4)
  - Reestimates and reconciliation, 1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 5)
  - Salomon Brothers Inc., 1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 6-7)
  - Salomon Brothers [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Simonson, David [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Strategic plan: 1984-1988, 1983 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 8)
  - Strategy and development, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 9-10)
  - Valuation, 1973-1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 11-12)
  - Van Amerongen, Lewis, 1983 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 13)
  - Van Amerongen, Lewis [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R16)
  - Weekly reports, 1984 (Offsite-box 605, Folder 14)
- Series III.B. Corporate Secretary: Federal Communications Commission Filings, 1957-1976; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Records include ownership reports for radio or television station licenses held by Time Inc. or its subsidiaries, including Sterling Manhattan Cable Television, filed with the Federal Communications Commission (FCC); information on shares of Time Inc. stock held by trusts in response to questions from the FCC; and background information on FCC rules and regulations as they affected Time Inc.
  The FCC filings were handled by staff who held positions both in the Corporate Secretary office and in the Comptroller's office including John F. Harvey, Charles Gleason, Curtis Messinger, and J. Winston Fowlkes. In the early 1970s, the filings were handled by Peter Sheppe as Director of Administration under the Comptroller's office. The later filings were handled by Sheppe as Assistant Secretary and his assistant Doris Laffan. At this time, Sheppe was not part of the Comptroller's office.
  This series remains in the original order of reports, trust data, and miscellanous. Reports and trust data have chronological arrangement within each set of folders.
  - Reports, 1957-1971 (Offsite-box 4251, Folder 1-19)
  - Reports, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 4252, Folder 1-13)
  - Trust data, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 4252, Folder 14-16)
  - Micellaneous, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 4252, Folder 17)
- Series III.C. Corporate Secretary: Securities and Exchange Commission Filings, 1963-1974; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filings include correspondence and forms regarding changes in the board of directors and other major events, details of mergers, purchase or sale of Time Inc. stock, and registration of securities. Forms filed include Form 4, Form S-8, Form 8-K and Form 10-K.
  The SEC filings were handled by staff who held positions both in the Corporate Secretary office and in the Comptroller's office including Assistant Secretary and Comptroller John F. Harvey, Assistant Secretary and Assistant Comptroller Curtis Messinger, and Assistant Secretary and Director of Administrative Services P. Peter Sheppe.
  Organized chronologically by year based on the original order.
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1963 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 1)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1964 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 2-5)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1965 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 6-8)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1966 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 9-11)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1967 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 12-14)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1968 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 15-17)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1969 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 17-20)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1970 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 21-26)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1971 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 27-31)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1972 (Offsite-box 877, Folder 32-33)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1972 (Offsite-box 878, Folder 1-7)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1973 (Offsite-box 878, Folder 8-14)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings: Temple merger, 1973 (Offsite-box 878, Folder 15-19)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings: Temple merger, 1973 (Offsite-box 879, Folder 1)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1973 (Offsite-box 879, Folder 2-4)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, 1974 (Offsite-box 879, Folder 5-18)
- Series III.D. Corporate Secretary Files on Employee Benefits Plans, 1938-1972; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  The Corporate Secretary files on employee benefits document implementation and changes in pension and retirement benefits, profit-sharing, life insurance and other employee benefits at Time Inc. Records include interoffice correspondence, reports from executive committees formed to explore trends in benefits, surveys on existing benefits plans, and plans from other companies. The majority of records come from Assistant Secretary William G. Davis, Jr. with very early records from Secretary David Brumbaugh, Assistant Secretary Arnold Carlson, and Allen Grover, vice president and assistant to co-founder Henry Luce. The file on Margaret Bourke-White details payments to her to make up for years she was not eligible to contribute to the company's retirement plan. Further information on employee benefits from later dates in is the Time Inc. Administration, Human Resources and Personnel Records (MS 3009-RG 17).
  Organized with "Changes" files in the front chronologically followed by files regarding other benefits remaining in the original order. The archivist reorganized the "Changes" folders from reverse chronological to chronological.
  - Changes: 1938 to 1941, 1938-1941 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 1-3)
  - Changes: 1941 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 4-6)
  - Changes: 1946 to 1952, 1941-1950 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 7-8)
  - Changes: 1951, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 9-10)
  - Changes: 1953: Work papers, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 11-12)
  - Changes: 1953: Other, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 13-14)
  - Changes: 1955 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 15)
  - Changes: 1956 to 1957, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 16)
  - Changes: 1961 to 1962, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 4213, Folder 17)
  - Changes: 1963 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 1)
  - Changes: 1971, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 2)
  - Changes: 1972 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 3)
  - Foreign: Canadian tax, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 4)
  - Foreign: London, 1946-1957 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 5)
  - Foreign: Paris: Group life insurance, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 6)
  - Foreign: Paris: Retirement, 1955-1958 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 7)
  - Foreign: MIscellaneous, 1949-1957 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1945-1952 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 9)
  - Procedures, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 10)
  - Trusts: Merger of prior trusts, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 11)
  - Trusts: Time employees' savings and profit-sharing, 1956 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 12)
  - Stock plans: Other companies, 1956 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 13)
  - [Stock plans:] Other companies, 1954-1959 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 14)
  - 1953 memorandum to board on retirement and profit-sharing plans from Brumbaugh, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 15)
  - Bourke-White, Margaret (special), 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 4214, Folder 16)
- Series IV.A. Finance Division: Chief Financial Officer: Thayer Bigelow Files, 1982-1987; 3.25 Linear feet in 5 record cartons, 1 flat box
  Thayer Bigelow began working for Time Inc. in 1967 in the Comptroller Office. In 1972, he left Time Inc. briefly to work for the Saturday Review Company. Bigelow returned to Time Inc. in 1973 to take the position of vice president and treasurer of Manhattan Cable Television, a Time Inc. subsidiary. He was promoted to and held the position of president of Manhattan Cable Television from 1976 to 1980. From 1980 to 1981, he moved to Time-Life Films and Video holding several titles, briefly serving as president of this group. He then became a corporate officer serving as vice president and treasurer of Time Inc. from 1982 to 1984 and chief financial officer (CFO) from 1984 to 1987. As CFO, he oversaw the entire Finance division including the treasurer and corporate controller (superseding the comptroller). He left the position of CFO to serve briefly as president of the Time Inc. subsidiary American Television and Communications Corporation (ATC). From 1988 to 1991, he served as the president of Home Box Office (HBO).
  The Thayer Bigelow Files include records created while he served as vice president and treasurer of Time Inc. from 1982 to 1984 and chief financial officer of Time Inc. from 1984 to 1987.
  Organized into two subseries: Subseries IV.A.1. Administrative Files and Subseries IV.A.2. Forest Products Group.
  - Subseries IV.A.1. Administrative Files, 1982-1987; 1.75 Linear feet in 3 record cartons, 1 flat box
    The administrative files subseries contain correspondence, reports, newsletters, clippings, notes, and transcripts of speeches as well as various other documents.
    - Allen Co. Shearson Lehman Confidentiality Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Asiaweek, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 1)
    - Board Meetings, 1986 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 2-8)
    - Board Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Budget Presentation: Corporate Finance, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 9)
    - Budget Presentation: Corporate Finance: 1985 (Offsite-box 4271, Folder 2-3)
    - CIBP Adjustment and Progress Report on LTIP, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 10)
    - Corporate Bonuses, 1984 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Bonuses [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Corporate Finance Bonuses, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Finance Bonuses [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Correspondence: Company Acquisition Proposals, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 13-16)
    - Dolan, Kevin, 1984 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 17)
    - Eurodollar Loan, 1983 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 18-19)
    - Eurodollar Loan [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Filmways/Orion, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 20)
    - Financing, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 21)
    - Fowlkes, Winston [RESTRICTED] (2 folders), 1984-1986 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Georgia Kraft, 1982 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 22)
    - Gold, 1985 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 23-24)
    - Minority Business Development, 1984 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 25)
    - Partial Redemption of Series B: Preferred Stock, 1984 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 26)
    - P&C [Property and casualty?] Presentation, 1984 (Offsite-box 648, Folder 27)
    - Personnel Compensation Committee Meeting, 1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 1)
    - Pioneer Press: Sale, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 2-3)
    - Pioneer Press: Sale [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Political Action Committee for Time Inc. (PAC), 1982 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 4)
    - Preferred Stock, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 5)
    - Preferred Stock [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Rockefeller Group, 1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 6)
    - Rothschild, N.M. & Sons, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 7)
    - Salomon Brothers Engagement Letter and Indemnification Letter [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Silver Screen, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 8)
    - Spin-off Proxy, 1984 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 9)
    - Time/Temple-Inland Agreements [RESTRICTED] (4 folders), 1984 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Temple-Inland Shares, 1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 10)
    - Temple-Inland Stock, 1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 11)
    - Time Inc. Foundation Audited Financial Statements: Ernest & Whitney, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 12)
    - TRASOP (Time Inc. Tax Reduction Act Stock Ownership Plan), 1982 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 13)
    - Washington Star Closedown, 1983 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 14)
    - Wheelabrator Frye [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R9)
    - WOTV Sale, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 15-16)
    - WOTV Sale [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Ziff-Davis, 1984 (Offsite-box 649, Folder 17)
  - Subseries IV.A.2. Forest Products Group Spin-off, 1982-1985; 1.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    The Forest Products Group Spin-off subseries contain reports that were compiled about the finances of Forest Products Group and their subsidiaries.
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Historical: Alternative Strategies for the Forest Products, 1982 (Offsite-box 623, Folder 1-2)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Expenses, 1984 (Offsite-box 623, Folder 3)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: August-October, 1983 (Offsite-box 623, Folder 4-6)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Press Coverage, 1983 (Offsite-box 623, Folder 7)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Kidder, Peabody & Co, 1983? (Offsite-box 623, Folder 8)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Seperation Analysis of Forest Product Group, 1985? (Offsite-box 623, Folder 9-11)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Seperation of Forest Product Group: Exhibits, 1983 (Offsite-box 623, Folder 12)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: Nick Nicholas on Dowalert, 1983 (Offsite-box 624, Folder 1)
      Includes audiovisual material. 1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape.
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: January-April, 1983 (Offsite-box 624, Folder 2-4)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: May, 1983 (Offsite-box 624, Folder 5-7)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: May [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: June-July, 1983 (Offsite-box 624, Folder 8-10)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: June-July [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: November-December, 1983 (Offsite-box 624, Folder 11-12)
    - Forest Products: Spin-off: November-December [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R9)
- Series IV.B. Finance Division: Treasurer Charles Stillman Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1954; 0.67 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Charles Stillman was an early staff member and officer of Time Inc. joining in 1928 as the business manager. He shortly was promoted to assistant treasurer. In 1930 he was elected the treasurer of Time Inc. Beginning in January 1949, he was both an executive vice president of the company as well as treasurer. Stillman joined the Time Inc. board of directors in 1948. From 1960 to 1968, he served as the chairman of the finance committee. Stillman retired from Time Inc. in 1970, but remained an advisory director to the board.
  Stillman took leave from Time Inc. for six months beginning in June 1948 to head the Technical Survey Mission for the China Aid Program at the request of the United States Economic Cooperation Administrator.
  The majority of the correspondence and memoranda in this series are to and from Charles Stillman while he was the treasurer of Time Inc., but look like they were removed from the files of other staff members, mainly President Roy E. Larsen. A note from the Time Inc. Archives accompanying the files says, "Retain these folders intact for Mr. Stillman." indicating that the Archives considered these Stillman's records although they were collected from other sources.
  Most of his interoffice memoranda are to the "War List" during World War II reporting on or giving commentary about financial, commodities, and labor issues during and due to the war, particularly issues that may affect Time Inc. or its subsidiaries and associated foreign publishers. The folder with memoranda from 1939 includes a list of staff on the various War Lists. Some memoranda include attachments of reports and other materials from outside organizations such as the Roundtable on National Defense and The Army Industrial College. There is also a small amount of correspondence during his work for the Economic Cooperation Administration.
  Some material was found loose and some was in existing folders. While the loose material could originally have been part of one of the folders, it has been house separately to maintain the original order since it isn't clear if some of the records were originally from Stillman.
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed. The War memoranda are organized chronologically based on the original arrangement with existing folders first followed by rehoused loose material.
  - Archives instructions, 1954 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 1)
  - Federal Economic Cooperation Administration mission: General, 1948 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 2)
  - Federal Economic Cooperation Administration mission: Press conference, 1948 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda: Donald F. Carpenter letter, 1949 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda: "Q" Department, 1942 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda: War, 1939-1940 July (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 6-7)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 August-October (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 November-1942 September (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 9-11)
  - Memoranda: War, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 July (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 August (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 September (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 October (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 16)
  - Memoranda: War, 1940 December-1941 September (Offsite-box 4211, Folder 17)
- Series IV.C. Finance Division: Investor Relations Files, 1922-1989 (bulk, 1970-1989); 7 Linear feet in 9 record cartons and 1 flat box
  The Investor Relations Files document Time Inc.'s correspondence with shareholders and its financial relationships with subsidiaries in terms of stock and investments. Of interest is a copy of the December 6, 1922 board meeting minutes and resolutions with an analysis of stockholders in the Manager of Corporate Analysis and Manager of Shareholder Relations Files.
  Organized into four subseries:
  Subseries IV.C.1. Vice President J. Winston Fowlkes files on Annual Reports and Investor Factbooks
  Subseries IV.C.2. Director: Allen Barr Files
  Subseries IV.C.3. Director: General files
  Subseries IV.C.4. Manager of Corporate Analysis and Manager of Shareholder Relations Files
  - Subseries IV.C.1. Vice President J. Winston Fowlkes files on Annual Reports and Investor Factbooks, 1984-1987; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    From 1970 through 1978, J. Winston Fowlkes served as the assistant treasurer for Time Inc. In 1979, he was promoted to treasurer. Fowlkes served as treasurer until 1983 when he became a vice president and director of investor relations within the Finance Division of the corporate group, a position in which he remained until 1986. Additionally, Fowlkes is listed as a member of Time Inc.'s 1984 and 1985 annual report committees. Fowlkes resigned from Time Inc. in February 1987. According to his correspondence, he transitioned into investment banking.
    Vice President J. Winston Fowlkes files document his work compiling information for inclusion in the Time Inc. annual reports and investor factbooks and organizing the printing. Records include memoranda from various other members of the annual reports committee and other staff, including annual reports publisher Edgar Smith, a retired vice president of Time Inc.; invoices; press releases of major company accomplishments and changes over that year; photographic material; meeting agenda; production timelines; reports on comments; and drafts of the annual reports.
    Organized chronologically based on the original arrangement.
    - Annual Report, 1984 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Report: Photography, 1984 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 3-4)
    - Investor Factbook, 1984 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 5-6)
    - Annual Report, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 7-16)
    - Annual Reports and Quarterlies of Other Companies, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 17)
    - Investor Factbook, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report: Financial, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report: President's Letter, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 20)
    - Year-End Income Statement Results, 1985 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 21)
    - Accounting Changes, 1986 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 22)
    - Financial Statements, 1986 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 23)
    - Annual Report: Letter to Shareholders: Stan Kapner, 1986 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 24)
    - Annual Report: Photographs, 1986 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting: Questions and Answers, 1986 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 26)
    - Investor Factbook, 1987 (Offsite-box 818, Folder 27)
  - Subseries IV.C.2. Director Allen Barr Files, 1983-1989; 5.25 Linear feet in 5 record cartons and 1 flat box